<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Thirty Days Of</string>
    <string name="expand_button_content_description">Click to see card info</string>
    <string name="title_1">Mega Knight</string>

    <string name="title_2">PEKKA</string>
    <string name="title_3">Inferno Dragon</string>
    <string name="title_4">Lumber Jack</string>
    <string name="title_5">Executioner</string>
    <string name="title_6">Goblin Drill</string>
    <string name="title_7">Arrows</string>
    <string name="title_8">Goblin Barrel</string>
    <string name="title_9">Bats</string>
    <string name="title_10">Bomber</string>
    <string name="title_11">Boss Bandit</string>
    <string name="title_12">Cannon</string>
    <string name="title_13">Electric Wizard</string>
    <string name="title_14">Fire Cracker</string>
    <string name="title_15">Witch</string>
    <string name="title_16">Ice Wizard</string>
    <string name="title_17">Knight</string>
    <string name="title_18">Log</string>
    <string name="title_19">Magic Archer</string>
    <string name="title_20">Mortar</string>
    <string name="title_21">Musketeer</string>
    <string name="title_22">Princess</string>
    <string name="title_23">Ram Rider</string>
    <string name="title_24">Royal Giant</string>
    <string name="title_25">Skeleton army</string>
    <string name="title_26">Skeleton King</string>
    <string name="title_27">Skeletons</string>
    <string name="title_28">Tesla</string>
    <string name="title_29">Valkyrie</string>
    <string name="title_30">Wizard</string>

    <string name="information_1">Mega Knight is a mighty beast with 3992 hit points and 268 damage.
        His speed is medium.</string>
    <string name="information_2">She has extremely high damage and hit points but is very slow
        and easy to distract with swarms, often requiring splash support. For 7 Elixir and her very
        high stats, shes very reliable for defense and tanking, and can devastate towers.</string>
    <string name="information_3">For 4 Elixir, this dragon has moderately high health and high
        damage. For 2 Cycles, if his Evolution is activated, he will gain a nice pair of goggles
        alongside a transparent fuel tank and unlock a new ability the Beam Momentum.</string>
    <string name="information_4">A powerful glass cannon for 4 Elixir, the Lumberjack provides
        high damage and speed with moderate hitpoints.  For 2 cycles, if his Evolution is active,
        after dropping his Rage, he will raise from the dead in the form of a spooky ghost.  </string>
    <string name="information_5">For 5 Elixir, he provides insane value with moderately high
        hitpoints and a sharp piercing axe that damages everything, ground or air, in its path for
        4 tiles. On top of that, his axe returns, dealing another swing of damage on the way
        back to him, dealing much more! </string>
    <string name="information_6">For 4 Elixir, this drill can pop up anywhere in the arena and
        start releasing Goblins. Upon destruction, it spawns 2 more! For 2 Cycles, if its Evolution
        is active, the Goblins will go under ground two times that when not next to the Crown
        Tower, will appear at the same spot </string>
    <string name="information_7">Shoot into the sky with a 3 Elixir rain of Arrows.
        Its moderate damage and large radius makes clearing swarms and weak enemies a breeze,
        but is lackluster against higher health units like the Knight.</string>
    <string name="information_8"> The Goblin Barrel is an Epic card that is unlocked from
        the Arena 6. It is a spell, once the spell has hit the ground, it spawns three Goblins.
        It is a wooden barrel with a Goblin logo on it. A Goblin Barrel card costs 3 Elixir to deploy.</string>
    <string name="information_9">Fragile but fast flying units, Bats can attack both ground and
        air units and their strong bites can easily deal with solo mini tanks. At just 2 Elixir,
        Bats can fortify and cheapen your deck. For 2 Cycles, if their Evolution is active,
        then they become VAMPIRE bats, granting them a new power called Life Leech,
        healing themselves whenever they attack! </string>
    <string name="information_10">A 2 Elixir high damage and medium ranged splash troop.</string>
    <string name="information_11">The Boss Bandit is a Champion card that is unlocked from the
        Royal Crypt (Arena 17). It spawns a single target, ground targeting, melee,
        ground troop with high hitpoints and high damage.</string>
    <string name="information_12">The Cannon is a Common card that is unlocked from the Barbarian
        Bowl Arena 3. It spawns a single target, ground targeting, medium ranged, building with
        moderate hitpoints and moderate damage. It appears as a cannon atop a metal platform with
        a wooden base that have legs connected by ropes. A Cannon card costs 3 Elixir to deploy.</string>
    <string name="information_13">The Electro Wizard is a Legendary card that is unlocked from the
        Electro Valley Arena 11. It spawns a fast, multi target, air targeting, medium ranged,
        ground troop with moderate hitpoints and moderate damage.An Electro Wizard card costs 4
        Elixir to deploy. </string>
    <string name="information_14">This former Archer has turned rebellious, bringing a firework
        to cause havoc in the arena, just to lit up the showdowns! While frail for 3 Elixir,
        she will push herself back with every attack.For 2 Cycles, if her Evolution is active,
        she gets fired up. Both her initial attack and her shrapnel fires lands sparks which deal
        damage around an area, and even slows down the movement speed of opposing troops!</string>
    <string name="information_15">While her health is only decent and splash damage is mediocre
        for 5 Elixir, she summons 4 Skeletons every 7 seconds to help distract destroy,
        making her useful for defense and support. </string>
    <string name="information_16">Chill out! This wizard has moderate hitpoints, deals low area
        damage that slows units and spawns with frost around him that slows enemies (and also deals tiny damage to boot). For 3 Elixir.</string>
    <string name="information_17">A moderate damage single target melee troop.</string>
    <string name="information_18">It rolls. It crushes. It knocks back. It makes those heads roll.
        It is none other than The Log. Arena floor, dealing moderate damage and knocking back every
        enemy ground unit in its path for just 2 Elixir.</string>
    <string name="information_19">The Magic Archer is a Legendary card that is unlocked from the
        Arena 13. It spawns an area damage, air targeting, long ranged, ground troop with
        moderate hitpoints and moderate damage.</string>
    <string name="information_20">The ability to snipe towers, its moderate hi tpoints, and the
        light cost of 4 Elixir make this building versatile, though its incredibly slow hit
        speed means it often needs additional support against any unit. For 2 Cycles, if its
        Evolution is active, a new ammunition arrives: Goblins!</string>
    <string name="information_21">A consistent 4 Elixir single target shot attacking both air and
        ground with fairly average stats.  For 2 Cycles, if her Evolution is active, she will gain a
        scope, that will let her shoot enemies INFINITELY away from her vertically.</string>
    <string name="information_22">The Princess is a Legendary card that is unlocked from the Arena 11.
        It spawns an area damage, air targeting, very long ranged, ground troop with low
        hitpoints and moderate damage.A Princess card costs 3 Elixir to deploy.</string>
    <string name="information_23">The Ram Rider is a Legendary card that is unlocked from the Arena 11.
        It spawns a single target, building targeting, melee, ground troop with high hitpoints and
        high damage. After she travels 2 tiles, she will begin to charge towards her target,
        and deals double damage if she hits the target whilst charging. A Ram Rider card costs 5
        Elixir to deploy.</string>
    <string name="information_24">The Royal Giant is a Common card that is unlocked from the Royal
        Arena Arena 7. It spawns a slow, single target, building targeting, medium ranged, ground
        troop with high hitpoints and high damage.A Royal Giant card costs 6 Elixir to deploy.</string>
    <string name="information_25">Fifteen skeletons for just 3 Elixir  this massive swarm can
        overwhelm single target enemy units in the blink of an eye! However, with their very
        low hit points, they can be easily taken out by area damage or even several ranged units,
        so they’re best used on defense with caution.</string>
    <string name="information_26">The Skeleton King is a Champion card that is unlocked from
        the Arena 16. It spawns an area damage, ground targeting, melee, ground troop with high
        hitpoints and moderate damage. Being a Champion card, he will stay out of the players
        card cycle while he is deployed, and only return once he is defeated.  A Skeleton King card
        costs 4 Elixir to deploy, and his ability costs an additional 2 Elixir to activate.</string>
    <string name="information_27">Three fast, low damage single target melee troops. They can
        distract enemies when timed right or just exist to cycle your deck for the cheap price of 1
        Elixir! For 2 Cycles, if their Evolution comes active when they attack, another Evolved
        Skeleton with a fresh ushanka gets summoned</string>
    <string name="information_28">For 4 Elixir, it has moderate health and damage, pulling
        everything to itself, so that it can zap enemies, although it will not stun like most
        electric based cards do. For 2 cycles, if its Evolution is active, the Tesla accumulates
        so much voltage, that it will begin to release all that it accumulated. </string>
    <string name="information_29">A 4 Elixir powerhouse with high health. This tough mini tank
        swings her axe 360 to take out swarms and support troops alike.For 2 Cycles, if her
        Evolution is active, every time she attacks, her axe spins also summon a whirlwind,
        pulling both ground and air units alike, dealing an additional damage value. </string>
    <string name="information_30">For 5 Elixir, the Wizard burns foes on the ground and in the air
        with heavy hitting fireballs that deal splash damage.For 1 cycle, if his Evolution is
        active, the Wizard exchanges his stylish hair in order to become
        studious of the arcane art of a spell shield, giving him extra protection
        from all sources of damage. </string>


</resources>